ROBERT SMITH

Java Software Engineer

Phone: (0123)-456-789 | Email: info@qwikresume.com | Website: Qwikresume.com

SUMMARY

Over 8 years of experience in Software development using Java, J2EE and Database in various areas like Requirements gathering, Analysis, Design, Development, Implementation and Maintenance. Demonstrated team leading abilities for 3+ years. Involved in Design, Coding, Unit Testing, Integration-support, System Integration Testing, and post-production support for Back-end (Core Java) and Web applications.

CORE COMPETENCIES

Java, Python, Applied Mathematics, Machine Learning, Amazon Web Services, Research, Matlab, Matlab.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Java Software Engineer

ABC Corporation - 2012 - 2015

Key Deliverables:

- Completed on-campus studies and currently taking distance education courses to complete a Masters Degree in Computer Science (Available for full-time, W-2 employment).
- MOBILY, Riyadh, Saudi Arabia 2010-2015 Saudi Arabian telecommunications company with approximately \$5 billion in annual revenue.
- Java Software Engineer Played key role in development and deployment of Master Data Management (MDM) project.
- Developed data models using addition and extension.
- Assessed and developed online integration services using customized transactions.
- Created JSF web application to interact with MDM service.
- Constructed XSLT set to transform EAI requests to MDM format requests.

Java Software Engineer

Delta Corporation - 2009 - 2012

Key Deliverables:

- Developed Java-based RESTful web services implemented using Spring, Hibernate and SQL Server database Involved in implementing the rules-based decision.
- Developed RentpaymentNow in less than a month that provides the decision to applicants in less than 5 seconds and allows.
- Designed and implemented REST-based APIs that follow standards and support JSON and XML data using Jboss RestEasy, Gson and JAXB Developed an android.
- Implemented parsers in Java that would parse data files in XML and CSV formats and update that information in the appropriate database tables.
- Designed and implemented the internal logistics service, including contract management and price management components.
- Dev platform Windows 2K, BEA Weblogic, Language/tool Java, J2EE, EJB, JSP, JBuilder.

ROBERT SMITH

Java Software Engineer

Phone: (0123)-456-789 | Email: info@qwikresume.com | Website: Qwikresume.com

 Ukraine Designed the look and feel of the client's eCommerce website Integrated the website with existing catalog fulfillment systems.

EDUCATION

Master Of Science